Tangled Ever After is a animation, comedy, action film directed by Nathan Greno.
The kingdom is in a festive mood as everyone gathers for
the royal wedding of Rapunzel and Flynn.
However, when Pascal and Maximus, as flower chameleon and ring bearer, respectively,
lose the gold bands, a frenzied search and recovery mission gets underway.
As the desperate duo tries to find the rings before anyone discovers that they’re missing, they leave behind a trail of
comical chaos that includes flying lanterns, a flock of doves, a wine barrel barricade and a very sticky finale.
Will Maximus and Pascal save the day and make it to the church in time?
And will they ever get Flynn’s nose right?
Rapunzel (voice), played by Mandy Moore.
Flynn Rider (voice), played by Zachary Levi.
Priest (voice), played by Alan Dale.
Short Thug (voice), played by Paul F. Tompkins.
Queen (voice), played by Kari Wahlgren.
Dove Caller (voice), played by Mark Allan Stewart.
Tangled Ever After is a 2012 American animated short film written and directed by Nathan Greno
and Byron Howard, serving as a sequel to the 2010 Disney animated film Tangled.
It premiered in theaters on January 13, 2012, before the 3D theatrical re-release of Beauty and the Beast,
and on Disney Channel followed by the premiere of The Princess and the Frog on March 23, 2012.
In fall 2012, the short was included as a bonus feature on the Diamond Edition of Cinderella, and was also released
three years later, on the Walt Disney Animation Studios Short Films Collection Blu-ray on August 18, 2015.
The short is also available as a stand-alone download on iTunes.
The story of the short, counting also the TV series produced 5 years later (otherwise it would take place just after the original film as originally intended), picks up approximately three years
after the events of Tangled, explored throughout Rapunzel's Tangled Adventure, from the television film, Tangled: Before Ever After to the three-part series finale, "Plus est en Vous".
In the short, the kingdom prepares for the long-awaited royal
wedding of Rapunzel and Eugene Fitzherbert.
However, chameleon Pascal and horse Maximus lose the wedding
rings, triggering a frenzied search to retrieve them.
Greno and Howard started the film after popular demand.
Among the film's voice actors are Mandy Moore, Zachary Levi, and Matt Nolan.
The film explores themes of princess, wedding ring, wedding, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.